#### Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/jeffreyclark-03395b84 (LinkedIn) www.northerntrust.com/assetservicing/united-states (Company)

#### Top Skills

Relationship Management Financial Analysis Sales Management

# Jeffrey Clark

SVP - Practice Executive-Large Corporate Group, East. The Northern Trust Company

Chicago, Illinois

#### Summary

I am the Practice Executive for Northern Trust's Large Corporate Group in the Eastern United States. In this capacity, I lead teams of banking and trust professionals who have responsibility for relationship management and business development activities for a wide range of corporate clients in the Eastern United States. Across the client portfolio, my team is responsible for \$500 billion, \$145 billion and \$6.5 billion in assets under custody, assets under management and loan commitments, respectively.

Prior to assuming my current role, I was a Division Manager within the Large Corporate Group and prior to that, I served as the Group Head for the National Banking Group within Corporate & Institutional Services for four and a half years. In this capacity, I managed three Corporate Banking Divisions which had business development, relationship management and credit underwriting responsibilities for approximately 375 corporate banking clients in the Northeast, Mid-Atlantic and Midwest regions of the country.

### Experience

Northern Trust Company Senior Vice President May 1996 - Present (24 years 3 months)

Manage team of trust and banking professionals covering large corporate clients in the Southeast.

Wells Fargo Vice President March 1992 - May 1996 (4 years 3 months)

KeyBank Credit Analyst August 1991 - March 1992 (8 months)

## Education

Kent State University
Bachelor of Business Administration (BBA), MBA, Finance,
General · (1985 - 1990)

Bryan High

Kent State University BBA, Finance, General